maxwell.com 2014-11-22

# Maxwell Technologies | Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Maxwell Technologies, Inc., along with its similarly controlled entities, (collectively "Maxwell" or "we") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This privacy policy ("Policy”) describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [www.maxwell.com](http://www.maxwell.com/) (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This Policy applies to information we collect:

  * On our Website; and
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and our Website and/or any underlying exchange affiliated with our Website; and
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from our Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and our Website; and
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

This Policy does not apply to information collected by:

  * Use offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Maxwell or any third party (including our affiliates); or
  * Any third party (including our affiliates), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on our Website.

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of our Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Policy periodically for updates.

### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on our Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features/register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use.  If we learn we have collected or received information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com).

### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number ("personal information");
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as, but not limited to, geographic location, demographic, or industry segment; and/or
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us;
  * Automatically as you navigate through our Website which may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

### Information You Provide to Us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website, including information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material, entering a contest or promotion sponsored by us, requesting further services or reporting a problem with our Website;
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us;
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes; and
  * Your search queries on the Website.

### Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website;
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

The information we collect automatically is statistical data [, and does not identify any individual]. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests;
  * Speed up your searches; and
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * 100% J2EE architecture
  * Linux-based production systems
  * Software as a service web-based application
  * High-availability Oracle database

We do not collect personal Information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

### Third-party Advertiser Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some advertisements on the Website are served by third-party advertisers, ad networks and ad servers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about our users. This may include information about users' behavior on this and other websites to serve them interested-based (behavioral) advertising. We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement, you should contact the responsible advertiser directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you;
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it;
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information;
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or adjust your user preferences in your account profile.  For more information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our affiliates;
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Maxwell's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Maxwell about our Website users is among the assets transferred;
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures (for more information, see _Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information_);
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it including, for example, if you give us an e-mail address to use the "e-mail a friend" feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and your e-mail address to the recipients;
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information;
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use [www.maxwell.com/about_us/terms-of-use](http://www.maxwell.com/about_us/terms-of-use) or [www.maxwell.com/about_us/terms-conditions](http://www.maxwell.com/about_us/terms-conditions) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Maxwell, our customers or others including, but limited to, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of our Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  

  * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data. You can also always opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com).    

  * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by [checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com). If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may send us a return e-mail asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.  

  * Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data.  You can also always adjust your user advertising preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com). For this opt-out to function, you must have your browser set to accept browser cookies.

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") on the NAI's website.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [E-MAIL ADDRESS][ or write us at: [info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com).

## Data Security

All data collected or used by our Website is hosted, processed and analyzed by resources within the United State of America.  We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards.  The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to this Policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date that this Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this Policy to check for any changes.

### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:   
[info@maxwell.com](mailto:info@maxwell.com).

_Version: 13 th December 2012_
